(Leonard(on phone):)and was curious
what your rate is.
(Leonard(on phone):)Really?
(Leonard(on phone):)Um, okay.
(Leonard(on phone):)Is there any kind of discount
for length of marriage?
'Cause we're just
talking hours here.
(Sheldon:)Hi.
Call you back.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Penny:)Can we talk?
(Leonard:)I would love that.
(Penny:)All right, look,
(Penny:)I'm sorry I said I was
okay with everything
(Penny:)before we got married.
(Penny:)I hate that we're
going through this,
(Penny:)but I don't know
what to do.
(Leonard:)If you don't mind
waiting for a Groupon,
we can try marriage counseling.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Leonard:)Hey, uh, buddy,
(Leonard:)can we have some privacy?
(Sheldon:)Oh, of course.
(Sheldon:)Wouldn't want to intrude.
(Sheldon:)This is yours.
(Penny:)Okay, when I'm
done with him,